By the way, Tom, last time this, this guy and this guy spoke, uh, was about February 2020, just before lockdown.
Everything was great, and Tom said these words, uh, "Stop me if this rings true for you.
I think I might know more about Harry Potter than J.K. Rowling.
I'm like obsessed with Harry Potter."
And those words have kind of settled in my mind.
So, Tom, are you ready?
Yes.
Can I just say something quickly?
I did a pub quiz the other day because I know you love pub quizzes big time.
Harry Potter, I've read all the books, I'm a huge fan.
It was the most ridiculous quiz I have ever done.
One of the questions was, who was the referee for like the 1964 Quidditch World Cup?
And Zendaya was like, I know that is ridiculous.
Yeah, I know.
Well, okay, well, this may be a walk in the park for you.
Alright, let's do this.
What is the name?
You also love Harry Potter, so let's do this together.
Please help him, please.
What is the name of Ron's rat?
Uh, um, you mean Peter Pettigrew?
But yeah, but I was like, do you mean when he turns into the bad guy or like?
I will accept Peter Pettigrew.
That's, that's written down here.
The answer is, wait, wait, his name, no, no, it's like, we're gonna get, we're gonna do all of your questions, so don't worry.
We're not going to run out of time.
Right, Sony.
It's something...
Scabbers!
Scabbers.
I said whiskers.
I was like, whiskers?
Scabbers!
You're alive!
I want to keep a closer eye on your pets, Ron.
Because I kept saying Crookshanks, but that's the cat, isn't it?
Next question.
What is the name of Hermione's cat?
Oh.
Crookshanks.
Yeah.
God, you were scared for a second there, weren't you?
Yeah, I was like, did I get that wrong?
You're right, Crookshanks.
You just ignore the mean little boy, Harry.
I mean, I would have also accepted it, technically not a cat, it's half cat, but that's fine.
What is the name of Hagrid's dog?
There's a theme here.
Oh, what?
Why are you asking?
I know it, I know it.
It came right to me from the back of my mind.
Then tell them.
It's Fang, his name's Fang.
What is it, Fang?
Are you impressed?
Okay, final.
What is the name of Neville Longbottom's pet toad?
I don't know.
I know it.
Trevor!
Oh my god, because I just remember him going, Trevor, Trevor!
I, I thought that might be like a properly unfair lesson.
It's so funny now that you say that.
It's so intense.
It's just in the back of my mind.
You've got to bring that forward.
That's a visceral memory.
Do you know what's so funny, though?
I can remember all of that stuff, but when I was at school, if you said to me, do a simultaneous equation, my brain was like, no.
Not happening.
I don't care how many times I've done it.
No, but I can tell you all the horcruxes, everything.
I'm genuinely impressed, and I should have written more difficult questions.
Here we are.
By the way, this is your gift for winning the Harry Potter quiz.
So much.
I put it on my tree.
It's a little, uh, it's a little Harry Potter.
Now, I know it's not Gryffindor.
I am in Gryffindor.
But here we go.
Thanks for watching.
If you enjoyed this video, don't forget to subscribe and click the bell icon to keep up to date.
You can listen to my Radio 1 movies and TV podcast, Screen Time, on BBC Sounds.
And you can find these interviews in full on BBC iPlayer by searching Movies with Ali Plum.